Jack: Hi Emma.
I’m back.
Where are you?
Emma: I’m upstairs in the bedroom.
I’m packing.
Jack: Packing?
Why?
Where are you going?
Emma: I’m going to stay with my mum.
Jack: Your mum?
What’s happened?
Emma: She’s had an accident.
She fell over in the street and she’s broken her leg.
Jack: How awful.
Poor thing.
Shall I make you a cup of tea?
Emma: That’d be lovely, thanks…
I’ve told my work I need the time off.
Jack: How long do you think you’ll have to stay?
Emma: I won’t come back… until the weekend, I don’t think.
Jack: Sorry, until when?
Emma: Until the weekend.
I’ll have to make sure she’s OK.
I’ve taken the children to my sister’s.
She’ll take them to school tomorrow morning.
Can you pick them up after school?
Jack: Of course I can.
Now don’t worry about anything.
OK?
Everything is going to be fine.
Here’s your tea and I’ll take your case downstairs.
Emma: Thanks, Jack.
The taxi’ll be here in five minutes.